A team like this
can't win.
It's just the beginning.
You're so sure.
I don't believe it.
Just wait and see.
Too much content.
Make it more detailed.
OK, I'll go first.
Let's go home.
Go home.
In the blink of an eye,
it's almost been a month since school started.
Ms. Zhong,
have you finished arranging
the seating chart for the monthly quiz?
Yes.
I'll send it to your email
for confirmation before I leave today.
Mr. Wang, how about your side?
The monthly quiz is coming up.
Students should
balance their
activities and study.
Some clubs
may distract them.
Don't worry, sir.
What are you nodding for?
Are you talking
about our basketball club?
How are the students
doing lately?
Everything's good, sir.
The friendly match is coming up.
Don't let it interfere with your study.
Gu Chenyang, you're the shooting guard.
You're responsible for the pace of the game.
Are you ready?
Zhou Yang, power forward.
The foundation of the team.
Yes, sir.
What about you?
Lin Qingyuan, point guard.
Li Haoyu, shooting guard.
No problem.
Xu Anbo, are you ready?
Xu Anbo,
your vision
and hand-eye coordination
make you fit for center.
Okay.
This is our first
friendly match.
Yibei,
go for it!
[Welcome to the inter-school]
[basketball friendly match.]
[Today's competitors]
[are]
[Yibei High School's team]
[and Shiyan No. 1 High School's team.]
[I hope both teams give their all]
to put on a
wonderful game for us.
Go for it!
Yibei, go for it!
Stay focused!
Defense!
Go for it!
Yibei, go for it!
Nice shot!
No. 1 Middle School, go for it!
[Everyone,]
[this is the second quarter]
[of the game between Yibei Middle School]
[and Qiming School.]
[Qiming is currently in the lead.]
Go Qiming!
Quick pass!
Go!
Defense!
[No. 5 from Yibei, Zhou Yang,]
[is a truly excellent]
[blue-collar player.]
[Welcome back to the third quarter]
[of Yibei Middle School]
[versus the Experimental School.]
[Gu Chenyang,]
[No. 77 from Yibei Middle School,]
[hand foul.]
[Two free throws.]
[Fourth foul.]
Lin Qingyuan.
One more foul and he's out.
Be careful.
No. 50 Li Haoyu
and No. 77 Lin Qingyuan
from Yibei Middle School
have fouled four times.
They must be
careful from now on.
This is the final quarter
of Yibei vs. Qiming.
[I must say,]
[this game,]
[Gu Chenyang from Yibei]
[has really stepped up.]
[But it's been]
[a huge drain on him.]
If you keep playing like this,
I honestly don't know
if the team will be disbanded
or my internship
will end first.
Alright, you all must be tired.
Go get some rest.
I'll go think about
how to keep the team going.
Goodbye, coach.
Gu Chenyang,
I've been training
the way you taught me for a long time.
Why can't I still make the three-pointer?
You need to keep practicing.
I can't practice anymore.
I practice every day after finishing my homework,
and even lift dumbbells.
I can't even pick up
beef balls when I eat.
You just ate less.
I practice every day
and don't have time to go out
with my buddies.
I'm too busy paying bills.
Friendly games
are just to let us find problems.
and we need more time to cooperate.
So when I'm done
with the Student Union,
I'll talk to Gu Chenyang
and figure out a solution.
So,
don't be discouraged.
Cheer up!
Gu Chenyang,
you didn't say a word
and just left like that?
I have a tennis class later.
Tennis class?
I thought
you cared most about the basketball club.
It turns out
we're just your backup.
If you have the energy to complain here,
you might as well practice your dumbbells.
I can tell from your shooting strength today
that you haven't practiced enough.
Alright, alright.
The captain has left.
Let's go.
How about having hot pot together?
Do you two want to go together?
So boring.
You are not lucky enough.
I'll go by myself.
Senior Zhou Yang
Is this the case
at the beginning of the basketball team?
A loose sand.
As you said, it's just the beginning.
Let's clean up this bottle first.
Today's game was lost,
and it's also my fault.
Was my attitude towards them
a bit too intense just now?
Stop showing your little white teeth.
Your saliva is about to drip on my face.
You're just mean and sharp with me.
Why don't you
treat others like this?
What are you doing here?
Someone just finished playing tennis,
so he's gotta come back and practice basketball.
I'm just here to watch the fun.
Hello, Mom.
[Son,]
[why haven't you come home yet?]
I'm... I'm tutoring a classmate.
Gu Chenyang,
I still don't get this problem.
Can you explain it to me again?
Is that Li Haoyu?
Come on the phone.
Hello, auntie.
How do you know it's me?
Do you think I can't tell
by your accent?
You've been coming here
for half a month
every summer vacation since elementary school.
How could I not recognize your voice?
Alright, alright.
I'm relieved that you two are together.
Take him to have a good time.
I'm hanging up.
Okay. Goodbye, aunt.
I didn't expect that aunt
still remembers my voice.
How could she not remember?
She likes you very much.
She said you are like her,
both unreliable.
By the way,
How's your dad?
Is he still
nagging you?
I should thank you.
I haven't told my family
about my basketball team.
How long do you plan to keep it a secret?
I'll wait until my dad comes back.
After all, our team has been losing lately.
It's not the right time.
Actually, I just
wanted to take a break
and think about
how to
solve the problem of the basketball team.
I think
you should solve
your own problem first.
Don't you want to go home?
No one cares about me at home.
What are you doing here?
Where did you come from?
Didn't you go
for hot pot alone?
We've been losing,
who's in the mood to eat alone?
Should we...
Perfect timing.
Let's go, I've got this.
So this is
what you've got?
a bunch of people eating instant noodles?
What a vibe!
Why hasn't Xu Anbo come yet?
His family of four eats well.
They don't care about this.
Instant noodles are also good.
Who you eat with
is more important than what you eat.
You know me.
Let's eat.
Yummy.
Didn't you just complain?
That was then.
This is now.
Cut the chatter. Dig in.
Hello?
[Your delivery has arrived.]
Coming.
Where is he going?
No idea.
Why do you take it?
He doesn't eat
junk food like this.
I'll eat it. Don't worry.
Gu Chenyang, you've changed.
You really start eating junk food.
I don't know what you like to eat,
so I order some for you.
As the team leader,
this is my first time treating you to dinner.
I shouldn't have
left early this afternoon.
I'm sorry.
I accept Gu Chenyang's apology.
What about you?
We must accept it.
I accept it for Xu Anbo, too.
Cheers.
Come on.
Xu Anbo didn't come.
What a pity!
Wait until later.
What?
The most important thing
in my secret base is
eating,
drinking,
and playing.
A band.
Later, everyone can go there
and pick an instrument
they like.
Let's rock tonight!
I can play the piano.
Try something else.
Someone's already taken it.
Keyboardist, Gu Chenyang.
Fine.
I can play a lot of instruments.
I'll go with
the bass.
Sure, bass player.
Lin Qingyuan.
What can you do?
Guitar.
I... I've never learned an instrument.
That's okay.
Try this.
Catch.
Give it a shake.
Right, this is really for you.
The division of labor is really clear.
I announce,
Pulse Star will be revived
for a limited time tonight.
Cheers.
Solo time.
Keyboard.
Bass.
Sand Hammer.
Next is my drummer,
Li Haoyu.
Solo part.
of the solos.
Now let's get ready
to cooperate.
Ready.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Where's the score?
What are we going to play?
I was too excited
just now.
I have a demo here.
Listen to it and play it directly.
The atmosphere is the priority.
When did you
start playing basketball?
In junior high.
With Li Haoyu?
To be honest,
the day I got him into the basketball club
was the first time we played together.
We had been
in a cold war for a long time.
What are you laughing at?
You two don't look like
being in a cold war.
Indeed.
He has a bad temper.
We fight as soon as we meet.
But I
really don't want to argue with him.
No, no, no.
I didn't mean that.
I mean you two
are like quarreling good friends.
You don't look like
estranged at all.
I think
this is how you two
get along.
By the way,
I heard that
you used to be the MVP
of the basketball team.
Sometimes it's Fu Bin Yan.
So what do you think
I should do
as the team captain
if we want to win the game?
I think
we should be a team,
just like tonight.
More than that.
We can't just hang out together,
we should also fight side by side.
So,
do you have any good ideas?
I have one.
Hello, sir.
Fu Bin Yan.
Mr. Tao.
I'm looking for you.
There's a training camp
for the math Olympiad team tomorrow.
The math teachers want to know
if you'd be willing to help out
as a teaching assistant.
Of course,
you'll get extra credit
for the experience.
Thank you, Ms. Tao.
But I'm afraid
I already have
my own plans for this vacation,
and they're pretty important.
I see.
Alright then.
Your plans are more important.
I understand.
You can go now.
Goodbye, Ms. Tao.
Goodbye.
What a coincidence!
You're here to clean your area too.
What a coincidence.
It's the four of us.
Wait a minute.
Is this a sign
that we're not
good enough for basketball
and should stick to sweeping?
Nonsense!
Don't say that.
Think positive, speak positive.
Got it?
Got it.
Good luck, good luck, take it.
Bad luck, bad luck, go away.
Good luck, good luck.
Joint training.
Coach Su is serious.
Coach Su, you haven't given up.
Of course, I want to become a permanent coach.
That's great.
Lin Qingyuan,
you're so lucky.
What are you waiting for? Go get some snacks.
Let's go.
We're going to train.
It's just for fun.
I have a feeling
this trip will be really exciting.
Let's go get some snacks.
Let's go.
Su, I'll leave it to you.
Good idea.
It's your good plan.
Keep going.
Okay.
I'm really...
Coach,
is there enough room for all of us?
What's going on?
Coach, can I come with you?
Get off, get off, get off.
Forget it, forget it.
Is there room?
This is my car.
Alright, stop complaining.
The bus broke down.
I'll go to the base to check in.
You guys
run along this road.
If you don't arrive in an hour,
you won't have any food.
An hour?
That's so far.
How is this possible?
The countdown begins.
Hou, let's go.
Let's go.
Coach.
Guys, make sure to apply sunscreen.
Okay.
Don't just stand there.
The countdown has started.
Why are you going too?
Stop looking, run quickly.
Let's go.
Hurry up, hurry up.